domainface.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy | Domainface

Read below for specifics, but basically what we're trying to convey here is that we're not going to sell your data to other people or use it for nefarious purposes. About the worst we might do is email you occasionally to tell you about something we feel you might find useful, or to let you know about a promotion we have on. We're not interested in giving others access to private stuff you put into Domainface. Make sure you're using virus checkers and stuff though- it's not our fault if someone steals your password.

* * *

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Face Software Ltd or Domainface is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Face Software Ltd will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### INFORMATION GATHERING AND USAGE

  * When you register for Domainface we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card.
  * Face Software Ltd uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
  * Your credit card details are not retained by Domainface. We use a third party specialist billing provider called Recurly, which is 100% PCI compliant and bills our customers via PayPal, which is also 100% PCI compliant. When adding credit card and billing information, we submit that data directly to Recurly for storage and processing and do not retain it on our own servers. You are free to remove that data at your convenience and discretion by logging into your associated Recurly account. More information on PCI compliance for Recurly can be found at <http://recurly.com/security>. PayPal PCI compliance information can be found at <https://www.paypal.com/pcicompliance>.

### COOKIES

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.
  * Cookies are required to use the Domainface service.
  * We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your Domainface account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

### DATA STORAGE

Face Software Ltd uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Domainface. Although Face Software Ltd owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Domainface application, you retain all rights to your data.

### DISCLOSURE

Face Software Ltd may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

### CHANGES

Face Software Ltd may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Domainface primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### QUESTIONS

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support at domainface.com
